(This series is a work of fiction inspired
by questions that arise within the human heart.)
(It is not intended to offend or pass judgment
on any beliefs, religions, or individuals.)
(Previous Chapter)
Kongkit was wrong for starting it,
but you two were at fault too.
The only wrong thing you did
was to help me,
and now you're screwed too.
Don't help me next time.
I don't have any friends.
You're the only one I know.
Lust means letting desire control us.
Wanna sneak out for some roti?
You really won't come?
Come on. I'll help you up.
What if you can't stop it?
Then you fight it.
THE SEVEN DEADLY SINS:
PRIDE, GREED, LUST, WRATH,
GLUTTONY, ENVY, SLOTH
LUST
Tan.
Tan!
What?
For New Year's break,
are you coming to my home?
I'll write to my mom,
so she can ask Father for permission.
Can I… let you know later?
Okay.
Ahem.
It's been… ten minutes
since my last confession.
You're such a tease.
For me, it's been a long time
since my last confession.
So long I can't even remember.
Then shouldn't you confess?
God wouldn't listen to me anyway.
But you?
What sins would you even have to confess?
The Gospel today is about repentance.
But in God's eyes, repentance
doesn't mean He will punish us.
It means He's waiting for us to come home.
We've all lost our way.
Lost because of ignorance.
Lost because of weakness.
And sometimes, we got lost
because we thought it was love.
Humans long for love
because God made us with His love.
Scripture says God is love.
When a human heart starts to beat,
it naturally begins to search for love.
But the question is,
does every kind of love
lead us closer to Him?
Father.
Yes?
If some feelings make you feel bad,
is that wrong, Father?
Sometimes it isn't wrong.
But it makes you afraid.
Afraid you'll do wrong.
Fear…
How do you deal with it?
When you're afraid,
do you run from it or stay with it?
What if I still don't know?
It's okay not to know.
God isn't in a rush
to get an answer from us.
Having feelings isn't a sin.
The struggle of coping with them
is what proves our faithfulness to God.
So don't be afraid to come back to God.
No matter what happens,
don't run from God.
God always understands us.
"Ticket to Heaven"
(Episode 3)
Tan.
What's up?
You're totally spacing out.
Lots of homework.
Come on, what's wrong?
Tell me.
I'm fine.
Fine, then.
Barth,
that's my textbook.
How about this?
Play a game with me.
If you win, I'll stop bugging you.
You better mean that.
I won.
Guess you have to tell me now.
Tell me right now.
Come on, Ta! Come on!
Go, go, go!
Yeah! Yeah!
That's how it's done!
Yay! Woo!
All right, take a break, everyone.
A kind parent treated all of us today.
Come on. Hand these out.
- Come on, hurry.
- Which color do you want?
Go on.
Come on, hurry.
No fighting over them.
- Kong.
- Yeah?
Look.
All right, everyone. Time's up.
Come on. Let's go.
Go shower and get ready for dinner.
Come on, give me the ball.
Kong, did you see my last shot?
I was like Beckham.
Wow. You're such a show-off, Ryu.
That last shot.
I thought you slipped
and the ball just happened to go in.
One more and I'd have had a hat trick.
Hey, Kong. You guys go ahead.
I'll catch up.
Okay.
They're all gone.
I was looking forward to having one.
Hey,
did you save this for me?
Thanks a lot.
Why?
What is it, Tanrak?
Why are you covering your nose?
Huh?
Do I stink?
I stink, right?
People sweat when they play football.
Sweat stinks. So what?
Sweat stinks, right?
Let me wipe it on you.
Come on. Just a little.
Come on.
What are you do–ow!
Tanrak!
Stop.
Come here.
It's common to get sweaty
when you play football.
Let me wipe it on you.
Help, please! Help!
Tan.
What did Master ask us to carry?
It's so damn heavy.
Where do we put this?
How do we set it up?
Maybe you…
leave some space
for people to walk through.
Move it a bit more.
Kong.
Then set that side up evenly.
Can I get some help over here?
Yes, Master.
Alright.
Take these and line them up over there.
Everyone else,
once you're done setting up,
sit with your vocal sections.
Go on.
Sit with your section.
Today, we have students
from several schools here.
You're all members of our church choir.
So welcome, everyone.
Some of you may have never met before.
Wait.
Where's Nat?
I'm not sure, Master.
Kongdech, you sing bass for him today.
Yes, Master.
Barth.
Let's check your vocal range.
Come on.
Everyone, give Barth a hand.
That's it.
Let's welcome our new member.
All right, tenor.
The highest note you'll probably sing is…
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
This one.
Go on.
Ha…
- Ha…
A bit more. Full voice.
Haaa.
Haaaaa.
You can do it.
Okay. Tenor it is.
All good?
We're missing one set.
One more set?
Tanrak. Can I have one set?
Take mine.
No, it's okay. I'll get it myself.
Hey, take mine.
Oh!
Whoa!
Shit, sorry.
Oh, take Cherry to the bathroom.
And you two, go get a mop.
Yes, Master.
Bring the mop over.
Once you're done eating,
please help clean up.
Let's decide what songs we'll sing.
Whoa. There they are.
Tan, look.
Wow!
That's our Christmas play couple
right there.
Joseph and the Virgin Mary.
What are you talking about?
Exactly, Kongdech.
Before you tease them,
ask if they even want to do it.
Come on, Master.
I play Joseph every year.
Let Barth do it this year.
What do you say, Barth?
Interested?
What do you say, Tan?
It's okay. You can tell me later.
Go on. Take a seat.
Give me some more song suggestions.
Jingle Bells.
Two more songs, please.
Joy to the World.
Thanks, Barth.
Master Win lent me a shirt.
Should I wash this and return it?
No need.
Uh…
Sorry again.
It's okay.
I'll leave this shirt
with Master Win
and have him return it to you.
Okay.
See you.
Let's go. It's getting late.
Tanrak.
Don't rush back yet.
Huh?
We didn't get to eat anything earlier,
did we?
No.
I'll take you to the market.
What? I'm not going.
Come on.
Hey, Kong.
You go ahead.
I'm going to the bathroom first.
Yeah, okay.
Ready? Let's go.
Oh, Tanrak!
What are you doing out here?
I…
We ran out of donuts.
So Master asked me to order more
for the choir club.
I see.
Hmm.
I don't think I have enough left.
What about these?
These are already reserved.
I have to deliver them
to a wedding early tomorrow.
I'll have to box them first
to see if there are any left.
Never mind then.
Well,
- Never mind. I…
- I can help box them up.
It might make things faster.
And maybe there'll be some left.
Well…
Good.
That would help. Come this way.
Come on.
What's your name?
Barth.
I brought you some more.
You don't need this one.
Thank you so much.
Hey.
If we sneak one,
do you think she'll notice?
Hey.
Close the door
and help me clean the kitchen.
Sorry, boys.
I didn't make extra dough.
Here.
There really is only one left.
Oh.
- Please take this to share.
- Thank you so much.
Get back safely.
Yes, ma'am.
Here.
Our pay for today.
We worked hard together.
So we should eat together.
Thanks.
Mm.
It's pretty yummy, right?
But it's so damn dry.
Yeah, it is.
What?
Nothing.
I just…
haven't seen you smile in a while.
Really?
I thought you were mad at me or something.
It's nothing.
If I did anything to upset you,
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
How can I not?
How am I not supposed to worry about it?
You know I don't have many friends.
In all of Magdalene House,
you're the only one
I can talk to about anything.
And I feel comfortable around you.
Same here.
Really?
Can you promise me?
From now on,
if something's wrong,
just tell me straight.
Ahem.
This is my body which is given for you.
Barth.
That's not funny.
God is so going to punish you.
I'm not scared.
A guy like me
isn't going to heaven anyway.
I'm just practicing.
Maybe one day I'll get to say Mass.
I'll be ready.
Yes, Father Bodin.
Wow.
Nope.
I really can't picture you like that.
Why?
Don't I look like I could be a priest?
Cheers.
My source tells me
you got Cherry's pager number.
What pager? That's bullshit.
My source also tells me
Cherry doesn't have a boyfriend.
Wrong again. She totally has a boyfriend.
So you did look into it, didn't you?
You better keep this buried.
If Master Phak finds out,
Father Arnon will hear about it for sure.
Is the pager story true?
Barth!
Whoa, Barth. You're so cool.
Behave yourself.
We are still in Magdalene House.
Oh, Tan.
Aren't you going to go to your friends?
Well.
They…
didn't come to see me.
Tanrak.
Dip it in red for me.
Hey, Ryu.
- What's up?
- Help Barth out.
Sure.
Easy-peasy.
Hold the ladder for me.
Hey, hey, Barth.
I saw it this evening.
Saw what?
Cherry.
You haven't been here long,
but you're certainly the coolest now.
- Is your hair color cool enough?
- Ow, shit!
Barth!
What the hell?
Tan, come hold the ladder instead.
I'm going to wash my hair.
What the hell?
Hey.
Hold the ladder for me.
Hold it. This is dangerous.
What?
Hey, you got it on me.
Only a little bit.
Come on. I'm not playing.
Hurry up, so we'll have time
to do something else.
Done.
Tan.
Do you think Barth likes Cherry?
How would I know?
But for me,
I don't know if Barth likes her,
but Cherry definitely likes Barth.
Really?
What makes you think that?
Come on, think about it.
If she wasn't into him,
would she come all the way to school?
Yeah. Ryu just told me.
I saw it with my own eyes.
- For real?
- Barth definitely likes Cherry first.
I think, at any rate,
Cherry must like Barth.
But whether Barth likes Cherry…
Barth is such a flirt.
I think Cherry definitely likes Barth.
- Barth likes her first.
- You can tell from her eyes.
And Barth's eyes when he talked to her?
I mean…
What's wrong?
Hurry up. I need to do my homework.
Tanrak.
Hurry. It's getting late.
There are mosquitoes everywhere.
They're biting me.
What mosquitoes?
Hey!
Where are they?
Barth, it's getting everywhere.
This helps keep mosquitoes away.
See? There are so many around here.
Barth.
What if you get bitten
and it leaves a mark?
If you're not helping, go away.
I am helping
by keeping mosquitoes away.
Fine. I'll help.
Tanrak.
Mm.
What is it?
Are you asleep?
I need to talk to you.
About Cherry.
Well…
Cherry asked me
to be in the Christmas play.
So…
it's up to you.
Decide for yourself.
I'm asking you because
well…
if you don't want me to do it, I won't.
What does it have to do with me?
It does.
I want you to be okay with it.
Tanrak.
What do you say?
Huh?
Well…
just do it.
Christmas only comes once a year.
What's wrong with you? Hm?
Didn't we say we'd be honest
with each other?
Hm?
Nothing's wrong.
Really.
Then act normal already.
Come on.
Hm?
Hmm.
See? This is normal.
Don't read too much into it, okay?
What's this?
“Tired from football?
I'm cheering you on, Ryu. From Eve.”
Is there more?
“I love hearing you sing ‘Season Change.'”
You're so cool, Ryu.
Hey, hey, hey. You guys better be careful.
If Master finds out,
you'll be in trouble.
I'm not scared.
What about you, Kong?
I saw Oh, Cherry's friend,
giving you a big smile.
What smile? You're making stuff up.
I'll go tell Master first, then.
Hey, Kong. Sorry.
Calm down. I was kidding.
You guys need to behave.
People already think
scholarship boys are all flirts.
I'm getting dragged into it too.
Can't help it.
I'm just that cool.
Wow. So cool.
Kong, deal with this cool guy.
Hey, Kong!
How's that, cool guy?
Where's the cool guy?
Don't!
So cool, right?
Hey, hey!
What are you doing?
You're making so much noise.
Nothing.
The boys are just playing around.
Go on.
Get back to whatever you need to do.
Oh, Tanrak.
I need to go to the church
for a rehearsal.
They are waiting.
Sure.
And…
where's Barth?
Ms. Ying asked him
to fix a computer in the teachers' room.
Okay.
When he's done, tell him to hurry over.
I'll go first.
Alright.
See you.
Tan.
Tanrak.
Wait up.
What took you so long?
And where did you get that bike?
Just get on. Hurry.
If we're late, we'll get scolded.
Hold on.
Whoa!
Can you ride?
Give me a push.
Go.
I was fine walking.
This might be even slower.
Hold on tight.
You know you complain a lot, right?
You're pretty heavy too.
I can't tell if that was faster or slower.
You complain so much.
Hurry up or Master Phak will yell at you.
Yeah.
Barth, hold this.
Stand closer together.
Try standing side by side.
Barth, move a little behind her.
I want to see if the colors match.
Okay, good.
Oh, go ahead and unwrap it.
This one comes with a sash too.
Okay.
Help me.
You can tie it tight.
Like this?
Are you messing with me?
No, I'm not.
Oh, Tanrak.
Aren't you going in?
Oh.
I don't want to disturb them.
You won't.
They're just trying on costumes.
Go on.
Master.
Please, can I be excused today?
Are you okay?
Well…
I think I have a headache.
I'm not feeling well.
Okay.
I'll cover music rehearsal for you today.
You should…
go rest.
Thank you.
Good. Good.
Hello, Master Win.
Hello.
How's it going?
Going well.
Barth, hold it there for now.
Is that okay, Oh?
Do we need to pin it?
That's right.
All right. Barth, try the costume on.
Why did you finish so early today?
I asked to leave early.
Were you slacking off?
You're pretty sneaky.
Must be another power dip.
Yeah.
It just started raining.
That's good. I'll sleep well tonight.
Are you sick?
Did you take medicine?
Mm.
What does “mm” mean?
Did you take it or not?
Do you have a fever?
Are you warm?
You do feel a bit warm.
Hand me the scoop.
Which scoop?
This scoop?
This isn't a normal scoop.
This one goes Scoopy-Doopy-Doo!
You're smiling. Are you really sick?
Maybe your fever's gone.
Huh?
You don't feel feverish.
Are you really sick?
Let me see.
It tickles.
You're not that warm.
Tickles? Good.
Stop it.
Hey, anyone, grab a flashlight
and go check.
Hey, if you're the last one out,
don't forget to turn off the lights.
Tanrak.
Tanrak, why are you running?
I'm not running.
You're running from yourself.
Tanrak!
Tanrak.
Are you hurt?
Can we just talk?
Hm?
I…
I have nothing to say.
You don't have things to say,
or you just don't dare say it?
Hm?
Don't do this, Barth.
Tanrak.
Whatever's on your mind, just tell me.
Please talk to me. I'm begging you.
I don't understand, Barth.
I don't know anything.
I don't even understand myself.
You do.
You're just scared to admit it,
aren't you?
Just now,
you…
felt what I felt too, didn't you?
Tanrak.
Will things never be the same now?
You know everything, don't you?
Know what?
That…
I'm not God's favorite son.
I don't understand.
I like guys.
Tanrak.
I like you.
Are you mad at me?
I'm not God's favorite son either.
(Next Episode)
Can you hear the voice inside your head?
No hesitation?
It's not like I'm unwavering.
Some things make my heart falter.
It's sad to have to keep it to yourself
when you like someone.
When I'm near you,
I can't control myself at all.
Are you happy though?
If you could choose,
would you choose this path?
I thought you'd take this more seriously.